Welcome you udaipur.com
available kar raha raha hoon that's why you should
people udaipur.com or our youtube
channel.com
[Music]
[Praise]
Hum iss product
[Music]
Insurance
critical analysis me kya hota hai 7 days
me
thik hai
[Music]
Survival period ke aswab se likh hua ki
30-10-60
[Music]
Mark ho ya [
Music]
Disease
[Music]
Hai and
tyre pun of 92 major in five
[Music]
Coverage
Usko aur sirf cancer ka cover chahiye toh only
cancer and blood disorders only heart
and blood vessels se cover s ko
add kar bhi
dekh sakte hai
yeh diff diff hai
but han cancer heart
[Praise]
[Music] Because of lower green because of hai hotness si dont mind [
Music]
Aap log ko samjh mein aa raha hai jo maazaar aa raha hai jo explain [
kar sakte ho [Music
]
[Music]
[Music] Apaar c r
de r tu
driving  Out of which who came in there,
both are sitting mentally
[Music]
So let's start with an critician class
so basically this is an critical illness cover karta hai
ye plan and we cover 92 inside it
[Music] if it is
divided then some
diseases in it will give 100% out and those who
[Music]
minor in lot of disturbance so I
request you to switch off your camera please
[Praise]
[Music]
and if
that major what is the definition, we will
tell you further
nine CR covering 92 major and minor
critical illness diseases and we have divided
major and minor
here for the customer and for
his benefit, for his flexibility,
we have divided it inside them so
almost made it so that the customer can choose,
he can decide which cohort he wants to go to,
right so one we sell here and
one we give our customer the comprehensive
so comprehensive  I am
looking at the punch pointers here, you are
looking at the cancer end
[music]
[praise]
nervous system and punch wire inside, so
now he needs the power of all these five things, he
needs all these powers, if it comes to his critical shield
plan then he will
cover all five of them for us, so number one
we give him the form, second he
tells me that I only need cancer and
blood test order, I don't need anything else, so
he can buy only the cancer and blood
disorder one from us, so don't buy only the cancer one
and only the cancer one,
if he tells me that I
only need the heart one, I do
n't need anything else.
So far we have three
ways in which we can set this plan for him,
one we will give him comprehension, second
we can give him cancer single,
third we can give him heart one
[music]
we can do a single, one we can do
comprehension which will cover entire, second
you can give him cancer only,
third you can give him heart one and
fourth you can give him a combination of heart and cancer, if
he asks me to
give me just normal system then
we cannot give it,
we cannot give it, so if he wants to go
independent then he can
take independence of cancer, he
can take independent of heart or he can take a combination of
heart and cancer or he
can remain comprehensive with us, so in this way
you can pitch him
different shots in front of him in different ways.
Angi to yahan tak kisi ko ko koi doubt hai, the
period which will be there will be a waiting period of 90 days, once
I would like to ask people because people out there in the
call, so I want people to
answer who can tell me
who will help me,
cancel heart, so you told two,
third one and fourth one you told
comprehensive, so token yahan tak kisi koi
doubt hai, okay, what
coverage am I providing inside this,
so what CR is covered, so see,
you need not to worry about it
and secondly my second question to all of you people
out there, how can I say critical analysis
CR covering in this plan, you can type in the
chat box, no need to, you can
write, no need to, you can remove yourself,
so how can I say critical analysis CR covering
in this plan,
you can write in the chat box, please, yes,
critical analysis, they are covering
in this plan
fast
[Music] see, this
plan has been divided into different categories
And
divided the disease into minor and major, let's see
what is the major critical
analysis and what is the minor of critical
analysis so this will also be okay from
you know if someone wants to go for an you do not
cover surgical procedures so in this
plan this cover surgical procedures also so
this cover
1616 surgical procedures so if someone
wants to take surgical procedures then he
can also take it, this is optional for him, this will have to be taken as an
add on if it is CBRT if it is a
major surgery will give
100% to you and if it is an un-surgery you
will get 50% so this is basically and advance
cover right and this has an option every C has an
option cover for
answer restore ka bhi hai but this can tell
you later on nine D USP of a product
this date see don't think you know there is no
survival period so there is no survival period in this, what is
it
Serum if I have taken any Hajj
plan and the date was diagnosed with the
critical right
of the products there is an initial waiting period if the
person undergoing Hajj you will not survive for 30 days or if the
person undergoing Hajj you will survive for 60 days and after that only the claim will be
released on the claim of
critical rate if the person does not have any
survival period if the diagnosis is made then
we will release the claim as soon as he is diagnosed
we will not wait for his survival so
he has to live for 30 days you are not there is any such
survival claim as soon as he is
diagnosed he will be given the money
[Music]
and in this plan he has an initial waiting
period of 90 days so if he has an
initial waiting period of 90 days then why not
bring a policy of 90 days we will not cover it for three months for
any kind of critical rate only
after that you will be provided coverage so
this  You have to keep in mind that the initial is
19, the batting period of the test is 92,
we cover the critical issues which we divide into
major and minor.
We will tell you that major and minor are done in
this way. Before that, let
us pay a little attention to the entry. So eligibility
criteria, what is the eligibility
criteria for this plan, right now we are going to give a
plan to 18 to 65, so 18
to 65 right nine CR is not covering other
kids, right now we are not covering kids,
so you have to keep in mind that 18 to 65 can
give a
plan for one year, two years and a maximum
policy of 3 years.
[Music]
Date CR
so we have the list of critical issues, date
CR covering every divided into major and
minor. So usko humne major me aur minor me divid kar hua hai, so man liye
sambaddi
taking around si
overage order, so my major is cancer of
specifieds and reality, so bone  A
transplant is either major or
minor, so if it is a major organ then
how much will we give to it, we will give
it 100%, and if it is a minor organ then we will give
it 25%,
right, so you have to keep this in mind, the second
organ is major,
so in major, you can see open heart
replacement and repair methods, this is
no different medical terminology, right,
and if we look at minor organs then
inside minor, all the little bit is up on the
screen, so if we look at minor organs then
inside minor, you will see complete hard block and third
degree hard block with paste maker and which
plastic pe humara camping will be ₹5 lakh, so
this is minor, so we have
converted diseases into major and minor, right,
this is about heart, similarly if we
look at major organs then in major organs, major organs will be major, if
any other organ transplant has happened then it will
come under major, kidney failure acquiring
regular dialysis will come under major, you know,
and stage long  If there is a failure, it will come under major.
So if you have to see which minor it will be, which
major it will be. This is the complete list that we can
share with you. For example, if you have a
spinal stroke, then
all this will be covered under major diseases. If there is
blindness, then this will give major coverage to minor
diseases. You know, you can see loss of vision, loss of sight, loss of eye, loss of hearing, loss of ear. So different [Music] So we cover that too. So that comes under our major. So what have we done? We have divided the disease into major and minor. And depending on whether the person is a
major or a minor,
we will give him the money accordingly. The
interesting thing here is that there is no
survival period. Other companies
also have a survival period, but
here the
money will be released
depending on the major. And
now we understand this with examples. So you will get more
clarity on how this plan
works.
So you know.  The insured can opt for any of the
critical illness buckets. For the plan
available at Inception, he
can opt for any critical illness bucket and
here our maximum coverage will be
40 lakhs, so the maximum
cover we will provide to our customers is 40 lakhs.
So the same in short paper will be
dependent independence.
For example, understand one more thing here which
I want to tell you is that suppose
we have given a comprehensive cover of 40 lakhs for example.
Suppose if any one of his co-morbidities gets exhausted,
he takes the cancer co-morbidity, then
his remaining cancer
co-morbidity will be closed and he will have to continue paying the remaining
premium. So
now tell me, let me show you once again the
system here,
for example, to make it easy and more simple.
For example,
he takes a combination of heart and blood
vessel and cancerous heart and  I have
taken a combination of both blood pressure and gauge,
I am audible, my voice is coming
[Music]
so make a little correction in it,
if you also die then Ramesh from Quantum Hospital
and also
thank you, you gave it and he dies during surgery, then
his phone will be credited or not, there is
no business, I
[Music]
only
Sir, there is the word disease in my policy,
this is also a little responsible, every policy has happened in an accident
and it is natural
[Music]
a friend of mine died in it
[Music] tell me they
wrote it like this, I am
notable to tell exactly
[Music] if it happens then you will not get it, you will
not get insurance, right now
assistant why do we take insurance,
first you take it on a concept, you
want to take it for yourself
and to cover these future risks,
for my finance, we have specific
cost of
its surgery, so from where he gets
identified and
tell me
in common insurance medical
[Music]
and if
we feel that something has happened in the world
or to him, then there is a
concept, you have to think that
you should have taken that less from you
[Praush]
[Music]
How does it work, please confirm it once,
ok
sir
name
first, the
house like now see these are the five buckets
in our policy, if any
company has ₹10 lakhs,
you have hard blood vessel end
very important point, someone has a
comprehensive policy for x amount of
sub insured,
normally critician policy, critical
policy
policy, this kind of policy, general insurance, if you have any
doubt related to this, I have told you
with example,
sir, do you get restoration in this,
and if we have paid that 10 lakhs for this, then the
customer cannot get that cover again,
so what happens to the restoration,
that too again
[Music]
50%
off please share it with me, actually sir, I will
share it in the group
only, he had
a serious coronary
artery disease in hard blood vessel end, he had to pay the claim in the fifth month
[Music]
25% off the claim amount
[Music] it
works like this,
25% in case of minor  We will pay 75%
in case of
X-HOT this will work ok
[Music]
Third
a 40 year old person has applied for cancer and
blood disorder but
also for the store Love
Rajand
he will
get the amount there but he will have to
renew it continuously no
doubt till here
Monica does another illustration so
here
above and managerial station questions
so here customer should not
add policy to us
now let's see here Mr Ram
Ramesh Prakash he had a stroke nervous
system
God in the fifth month policy term
any
amount
you disease of heart and blood vessels so
understand from 700
you connect your customer with us my
only point is if you have any doubt then please take your
time
you can also tell us a little if any medical
language
you are very clear about this product
I am very g what happened
finally after this
our
[Music] which
comes
in original is under coverage so
you will get it  Accordingly the percentage or
% or it is always there,
look at the hospital. There are 15
four types of policies which is an
income
for the customer, there should be
a medical policy for the
customer and you
can debate this
and send this
line
that any plan for us
Vikas ji, right now turn on your video, I did
not understand the 9 conditions written by Sangam ji, regarding them no sir, I
mean Sangam Pandey ji you have written no, then
what does your nine mean, I have
understood the product here,
no, I am taking new operation, I am
not getting your voice Vikas ji, I am
interacting with Gaurav, there was a
lot of discussion in Gaurav policy regarding foreign policy and I have sorted out the
date point,
Monica ji, my voice is coming, now
whatever you
say, sir, make a video
[Music]
brother, because the
product is not your getting identity
[Music] which get in
critical in this
but the
coverage there is an different
but creation
up, so we have just explained it to you, it
accepts the thoughts,
that is suggested  You go for the receipt
police
[music]
[applause]